准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
口气
分镜总监
分镜
翻译: 1440kHz
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
日历
星期天
今天星期天  小蜗
It's Sunday, Gary
猜猜早餐要吃什么
Guess what's for breakfast
小蜗
没错
That's right
吃圣代
A sundae
冰淇淋好像没了
Looks like we're out of ice cream
只能换别的东西做圣代了
Guess I'll have to use something else
番茄酱
Ketchup
香蕉  樱桃
Bananas, cherries
没意思
Boring
有了
Here we go
洋葱
Onions
准备好了吗  小蜗
Ready, Gary?
洋葱
再加一样东西
Just one more thing
花生
Peanuts
小蜗  我们的花生罐空了
Gary, our peanuts jar is totally empty
等等
Wait
我知道还有一个能找到花生的地方
I know one other place we can find peanuts
幸好我窗台还种了这株花生盆栽
Good thing I still have these
peanut plants growing in the windowsill
口感不太一样没啥大不了
A little texture never hurt
做好了
There we go
圣代一定会非常好吃
This sundae's going to taste great
你不来一起吃吗  小蜗
Aren't you going to help me, Gary?
小蜗
Gary?
好吧
Oh, well
我能多吃了
More for me
俗话说得好  小蜗
You know what they say, Gary
我轻松得宛如星期天的清晨
I'm easy like Sunday morning
清晨
好  来看看我的待办事项单
OK, let's see my to do list
去工作
Go to work
这样可不对
No, that's not right
得要适合星期天做的事
I need the one for Sunday
有了
Here we go
跟裤头村的所有人打招呼
Say hi to everyone in Bikini Bottom
你好
Hello
某些人连星期天都会迟到
Some people are even late on Sunday
邮件
嗨  邮递鱼
Hi, Mail Fish
嗨  交警
Hi, Mrs. Crossing Guard
我的妈啊
Mother of mercy
有游行
A parade
嗨  游行队伍
Hi, parade
嗨  大号手
Hi, tuba player
嗨  鼓手
Hi, drummer
嗨  拿着钹的
Hi, guy with the cymbals
嗨  小号手
Hi, trumpeter
嗨  敲铃鼓的女孩
Hi, tambourine girl
嗨  定音鼓手
Hi, timpani man
嗨  迪吉里杜管手
Hi, didgeridoo player
[ 迪吉里杜管：澳洲原住民乐器 ]
嗨  打三角铁的
Hi, triangle player
嗨  拿着定音鼓的
Hi, guy with the kettledrum
嗨  弹钢琴的
Hi, pianist
嗨  吹笛子的
Hi, guy with the flute
你们大家好
And hello, Dolly
我的腿
My leg
天啊
Oh, my
我说错话了吗
Was is something I said?
今天有点不大对劲
Something weird is going on today
大家都在躲着我
Everyone's running away from me
公交
现在还有一大坨泡泡糖
And now giant piles of bubblegum?
太怪了吧
What next?
嗨  海绵宝宝
Hi, SpongeBob
嗨  派大星
Hi, Patrick
我好疑惑
I'm confused
我也是
Yes, I am
派大星  大家都在躲着我
Patrick, everyone is running away from me
看好了
Watch
嗨  大楼
Hi, building
我不明白
I just don't get it
我也是
I don't either
可能是你穿着不得体
Maybe it's the way you're dressed
才不会
Nah
可能是你声音难听
Maybe it's your voice
真好笑  派大星
Good one, Patrick
那就可能是因为你很丑
Well, maybe it's just because you're ugly
丑
Ugly?
你一定是在开玩笑
You gotta be kidding me
最好做个照镜测试
Better try the reflection test
嗨
Hi
丑
Ugly
不会吧
Oh, no
我不可能会丑
I can't be ugly
不可能
I can't be
不可能丑
I can't be ugly
我丑吗
Am I ugly?
我的眼睛
My eyes
我很丑
I'm ugly
海绵宝宝  我能不能借点浴珠
SpongeBob, can I borrow some bath beads?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob?
走开
Go
像其他人那样躲着我吧
Run away like all the others
没人想要像我这样丑的朋友
No one would want a friend as ugly as I am
那些人当然想了
Sure they would
你的丑陋会让他们对自己长相更自信
It makes them feel better about the way they look
讲个故事应该可以让你振作起来
Maybe a story will cheer you up
这个故事叫  丑陋的藤壶
It's called "The Ugly Barnacle"
从前  有一只丑陋的藤壶
Once, there was an ugly barnacle
他把大家都丑死了
He was so ugly that everyone died
讲完了
The end
那样一点用都没有
That didn't help at all
多久了
How long?
我已经丑多久了  派大星
How long have I been ugly, Patrick?
自打我记事起
As long as I can remember
你这个可怜的丑东西
You poor ugly thing, you
救救我
Help me
我羞愧难当
I'm so ashamed
生活跌入谷底
I'm spiralling
谢谢  派大星
Thanks, Patrick
可以了  派大星
It's OK, Patrick
不跌了
Spiralling over
学我应对问题的办法
Just do what I do when I have problems
喊出来
Scream
兄弟快来
Come on, buddy
我来帮你
I'll help you
好  说出来
OK now, say it
说出来
Say it
不行
I can't
海绵宝宝  你要想心里舒服点
SpongeBob, you're never going to feel better
就别把东西堵胸口上
until you get this thing off your chest
我知道  派大星
I know, Patrick
说出来
Say it
我很丑
I'm ugly
你很丑  而且还什么
You're ugly and what?
方正
Square?
不对
No
自豪
Proud
我很丑  而且很自豪
I'm ugly, and I'm proud
好
Good
大声点
Say it louder
我很丑  而且很自豪
I'm ugly, and I'm proud
再大声
Louder
我很丑  而且很自豪
I'm ugly, and I'm proud
再大声
Louder
我很丑  而且很自豪
I'm ugly, and I'm proud
I am ugly, and I'm proud
我很丑  而且很自豪
I'm ugly, and I'm proud
他是这么说的吗
Is that what he calls it?
感觉好极了
That felt great
全身充满力量
I feel empowered
那你现在想干什么
So what do you want to do now
不知道
I don't know
看电影怎么样
How about a movie?
礁石影院
不好意思
Pardon me
丑陋海绵借过
Ugly sponge coming through
大家尊重自尊自爱的美德
People respect self-esteem
嗨
Hi
虽然我很丑
I'm very ugly
但你一样也要安心看电影
but you should enjoy the movie anyway
不好意思  先生
Excuse me, sir
希望我的丑陋不会打扰到你
I hope my horrible ugliness
won't be a distraction to you
没关系  孩子
Not at all, boy
别管他的事了  海绵宝宝
Don't worry about him, SpongeBob
他就一
He's just a--
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
海绵宝宝  怎么了
SpongeBob, what's wrong?
我做不到  派大星
I can't do this, Patrick
我试了又试  可
I've tried, and I've tried, but--
我的自信还只是停留在表面工夫
I'm not always as confident as I look
我还是回去躲起来比较好
Maybe I better just go back and hide
你们有什么毛病
What is wrong with you people?
害怕看他的丑脸吗
Afraid to look ugliness in the face?
那就看
Well, here
给我看
Look at it
是不是很丑
It's ugly, isn't it?
你们给我看
You look at it
你们好
Hello
你们给我看
You look at it
嗨
Hi
给我看
Look at it
你们大家都给我看
I want all of you to look at it
他们全跑了  派大星
They all ran away, Patrick
零食吧那边肯定没人排队了
I bet there's no line at the snack bar
零食
有人吗
Hello?
员工肯定是去休息了
They must be on break
等等  派大星
Wait, Patrick
我刚记起来
I just remembered
我带了点花生洋葱圣代  可以分着吃
I've got some of my peanut onion sundae we can share
看着就好吃
That looks great
我得去趟厕所
I gotta go to the restroom
我肥皂用完了
I'm out of soap
能借用
Could I borrow--
退后
Stay back
我只是要点
I just want some
拿去
Here
我的钱拿去
Here's my money
你收下
Take it
收下  然后马上走
Take it, and go away
我手没那么脏的
My hands aren't that dirty
你们想不想听个厕所笑话
Do you guys want to hear a bathroom joke?
你是想杀了我们吗
You trying to kill us?
太可笑了
That's ridiculous
我被传染丑了
I got the ugly
派大星  里面没事吧
Patrick, is everything OK in here?
你在里面干什么  派大星
What are you doing in there, Patrick?
你不想知道吗
Wouldn't you like to know?
你头上为什么套了个袋子
And why is that bag on your head?
为什么
Why?
没为什么
No reason
除了你把丑传染给我了
Except you gave me the ugly
我要怎么办才好
Well, what am I going to do?
我可不能这样子出去见人
I can't go out looking like this
想想我们刚刚还说过的话
Just remember what we talked about
自豪力量大
There's power in pride
对你来说可能没事
That may be fine for you
可我原先长相特漂亮
but I was one of the beautiful people
现在看看我
Now look at me
我几乎都跟你一样丑了
I'm almost as ugly as you
我一直都在想  要是我跟那位一样丑
I always thought, if I was as ugly as that guy
都不知道要怎么办才好了
I don't know what I would do
派大星
Patrick
我妈会怎么说我
What's my mom going to say?
派大星
Patrick
我的天啊  要是我姐姐发现
Oh, my gosh, if my sister finds out
派大星
Patrick
等等  我没有姐姐
Wait, I don't have a sister
要是银行
If the bank--
派大星
Patrick
虽然鞋子差或者头发差是一回事
I mean it's one thing if you have bad shoes
or even bad hair
可是
but--
派大星
Patrick
你不丑
You're not ugly
是你口气臭
Your breath stinks
太臭了
Really bad
这下放心了
What a relief
真见鬼  派大星
Barnacles, Patrick
你吃什么了
what did you eat?
一点烤牛肉
Some roast beef
一点鸡肉
some chicken
一份披萨
a pizza
不对  我是说
No, I mean
你早上吃的啥
just the morning
一点烤牛肉
Some roast beef
一点鸡肉
some chicken
一份披萨
a pizza
还有呢
What else?
我吃了点你的圣代
Well, I had some of your sundae
圣代
Sundae
派大星  是我圣代让我们口气特别臭
Patrick, my sundae gave us rancid breath
什么意思
What do you mean?
意思就是  我们不丑
I mean, we're not ugly
我们很臭
We just stink
臭
Stink?
我们很臭
We stink
假发
你猜怎么着  章鱼哥
Guess what, Squidward
我们很臭
We stink
对
Yeah
好
Yes
我很臭
I stink
恶臭
I reek
闻我
Smell me
珍珍爱管事
导演
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜总监
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
插曲演唱
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
注意
Attention
全体蟹堡王员工  请注意
All Krusty Krew employees, attention
动作都给我快一点
Get the anchors out of your pants
到我办公室报到
and report to me office
事情就是这样
That will be all
我要宣布一件重要的事
I have an important announcement to make
万岁
Hooray
新锅铲到了
The new spatulas are here
坐下  小子
Sit down, boy
没有新锅铲
There's no new spatulas
太失望了
How disappointing
你们都知道我女儿珍珍
You men know me daughter, Pearl
她长得特别快
She's growing up fast
就好像我昨天才教她跃出水面一样
It seems like it was just yesterday
I was teaching her how to breach
我的哺乳类小天使
Me mammalian angel
总之
Anyway, uh
她暑假期间要来蟹堡王打工
so she's going to be working here
during her summer vacation
她有不少新鲜点子
She's got a lot of fresh ideas
可以引来饿肚子的新客
to bring in some hungry customers
你好
Hello
老爸
Daddy?
她来了
There she blows
海绵宝宝  知不知道这表示什么意思
SpongeBob, do you realize what this means?
没有新锅铲了
No new spatulas
错
No
意思就是
It means
会有没礼貌青少年要来教我们做事
some bratty teenager's coming in here
to tell us what to do
那种事绝对不能有
We can't have that
我们年纪比她大  对吧
We have seniority, right?
对
Right
所以我们要齐心协力
So we'll work together to
保护我们可悲的职位
protect our pathetic positions
明白  章鱼哥
Okie dokie, Squidward
然后新锅铲就能到手了
And then we'll get those new spatulas
好了  各位
All right, men
跟我的珍珍打个招呼
Say hello to me Pearl
你好  柱柱
Hello, Pole
大家好
Hi, guys
我十分高兴
It makes me jolly as a roger
你终于来参与家族产业了
to finally have you aboard the family business
太好了  爸
Great, Dad
因为我有不少新点子
because I have so many new ideas
我已经能闻到钱的味道了
I can smell the money already
要找我的话就来办公室
I'll be in my office if you need me
盒子里有什么
What's in the box?
是惊喜
It's a surprise
我喜欢惊喜
I like surprises
好
Great
然后闭上眼睛
Then close your eyes
我准备好了
I'm ready
目前还算喜欢
Well, I like it so far
哒哒
Ta-da
这是新款蟹堡王员工服
It's the new Krusty Krew uniform
我自己设计的
I designed it myself
好
OK
机会来了  海绵宝宝
This is it, SpongeBob
快跟她说你对新员工服的真正感受
Now tell her how you really feel about that uniform
好  章鱼哥
OK, Squidward
珍珍  这是史上最棒的制服了
Pearl, this is the greatest uniform ever
真该死
Fish paste
海绵宝宝  你样子好可爱
Oh, SpongeBob, you look so adorable
我都能把你吃掉了
I could just eat you up
抱歉  珍珍
Sorry, Pearl
本品不在菜单上
this item's not on the menu
虽说这不太可能  海绵宝宝
Well, I didn't think it was possible, SpongeBob
可你样子比平常还要可笑
but you look even more ridiculous than usual
别嫉妒人家  章鱼叔
Don't be jealous, Uncle Squiddy
我也给你做了一套哦
I made one for you, too
免了吧
Don't bother
只有傻子才会去穿
Only a fool would wear that
停航  船员们
Avast, ye shipmates
新员工服是不是让你们很震撼啊
Don't these just shiver your timbers?
赶快穿上  水手
Get that suit on, sailor
这可是花了钱的
It's already been paid for
暴怒
Rage
气愤
Fury
恼火
Irritation
丢脸
Humiliation
章鱼哥真是个缺心眼的
Squidward is such a barnacle
老古板一个
A stick in the sand
不过你不一样  海绵宝宝
But not you, SpongeBob
你可有型了
You are full of style
我
Me?
真的吗
Really?
没错  海绵宝宝
Totally, SB
你洋溢着时尚气息
You ooze fashion
而且我对这老地方有些特炫的概念
And I've got some completely coral concepts
for this old joint
我需要有你这样的天赋的人
And I'm going to need someone with your kind of talent
来给我帮忙
to help me
我一直都在帮蟹老板
Well, I have been trying to get Mr. Krabs
给这地方改一改
to make some changes around here
有了我的女生天性还有你的
Why, with my girlish instincts and your, um
海绵性
sponginess
我们就能把这个破烂餐厅
we'll turn this worn out lunch waggon
变成青少年天堂
into a teenage paradise
海绵宝宝  你更喜欢哪个
SpongeBob, what do you like better--
萌堡王还是怪堡王
the Kutie Krab or the Kooky Krab?
这是要干什么
For what?
容我问一下
Dare I ask
换了新面貌就要取个新名字
The new name for our new look
蟹堡王这个旧名字还是弃了吧
I mean, the Krusty Krab has got to go
名字一听就屑  谁还会来这吃饭
Who wants to eat at a place they think is crusty?
确实  名字起得很烂
Well, sure, it's a terrible name
可这地方也很烂
but this is a terrible place
因此名字的事就别去管了
Therefore, the name should be left alone
对吧  海绵宝宝
Right, SpongeBob?
有了
I got it
乱堡王怎么样
How about the Khaotic Krab?
亲堡王怎么样
How about the Kissy Krab?
皇堡王
The King Krab
糖堡王
The Kandy Krab
酷堡王
The Kool Krab
或者牛仔堡王
or the Kowboy Krab
卷堡王
The Kurly Krab
恐堡王
The Kreepy Krab
杀堡王
The Killer Krab
不行
No
确实
You're right
太恐怖了
Too scary
抱堡王
The Kuddly Krab
老螃蟹把蟹堡王卖出去了  真是可惜
It's a shame old man Krab sold the Krusty Krab
实在太可惜了
It's a darn shame
小姐  你知道
Hey, lady, do you know
这附近哪里可以吃饭吗
where we can get something to eat around here?
就这样了  我不干了
That's it, I quit
总算有青少年专属的酷地方了
Finally a cool place for teens
舒心感觉时刻在
Feeling so good all-around
可以好好在这放开了耍
to just, you know, hang out
珍珍  你可真是个天才
Pearl, you're a genius
知道有这座神奇小镇
Think you got such a magical town
这些年轻新潮的新客都来了
All these young, hip new customers
数天前我游向远方
I swam so far the other day
章鱼哥太土了
Phooey on Squidward
完全跟不上时代
He can't keep up with the times
想找到这神奇的地方
To try to find this magical place
你可真有见识  珍珍
You're a true visionary, Pearl
谢谢  海绵宝宝
Thank you, SpongeBob
视力正常  见得确实多
距离一定很遥远
I do have 20/20 vision
It's gotta be at somewhere far
新潮客也得吃东西
Well, hip people have to eat, too
还有鱼儿在畅游
Somewhere down where all the fish are
我回烤架那边去了
Back to the grill
客人也许兴奋热情
The customers may be hot
总有一天我可以找到
Someday, I'll find it if I keep trying
不过我烤架可更热
but my grill is hotter
海绵宝宝  点餐
SpongeBob, order up
在路上我会时刻微笑
Until then, I'll just keep smiling
两份沙拉
Two salads
想想我到过的地方
Thinking about the places I've been
从来没听过
Never heard of it
我得潮下去
I gotta stay hip
当我在梦中徘徊
While moving around inside my dreams
可不能落得笨蛋老章鱼那种下场
I don't want to end up like silly old Squidward
可沙拉到底是个什么东西
But what in the name of Davy Jones's locker is a salad?
色彩在波浪下舞动
Colors dance beneath the waves
美好一天美好结束
Such a beautiful end to a beautiful day
上菜了
Here you go
两份沙拉
Two salads
恶心
Gross
舒心感觉时刻在
Feeling so good all-around
这种东西可不是沙拉
Those aren't salads
快拿回去
Take those back
去掉面包  肉饼
Remove the bun, the patty
知道有这座神奇小镇
Think you got such a magical town
还有调料
and the condiments
可这样就只剩生菜跟番茄了
But that leaves just lettuce and tomato
没错
Exactly
好
All right
行
OK
没面包
No buns
很新潮
That's hip
没肉饼
No patties
太潮了
Happening
好  这绝对是我见过最酷的菜品了
Oh, yeah, that's definitely the coolest meal I ever saw
太酷了
This is so cool
两份沙拉
Two salads
太可怕了
That was awful
希望我以后
I hope I never
再也不会把好端端的蟹黄堡分开了
have to tear apart
a perfectly good Krabby Patty ever again
我的小心脏可受不住
I don't think my heart can take it
烤架哪去了
Where's the grill?
拜托  海绵宝宝
Come on, SpongeBob
你可潮了
you're a hip guy
油炸食品已经过气了
You know fried foods are O-U-T, out
说得对
Right on
快看我定的新菜单
Check out this new menu I came up with
沙拉和茶
Salad and tea
抱堡王菜单
可蟹黄堡哪去了
But where are the Krabby patties?
笨蛋  那种东西可不潮
Silly, those aren't hip
那玩意再也用不着了
You won't be needing that thing anymore
可
B--
总之有件更有意思的事情要让你去做
I've got something more fun for you to do, anyway
兄弟  要搭便车吗
Hey, buddy, you need a ride?
我要去大傻蛋大会
I was just on my way to the big doofus convention
太丢脸了
This is humiliating
我是煎炸厨师  该死
I'm a fry cook, darn it
你可以拿走我的锅铲
You can take away my spatula
可要是你拿走我的尊严
but when you take away my dignity
我就要生气了
that's when I get mad
我要冲进蟹老板的办公室
I'm going to march right into Mr. Krabs's office
跟他说这样太过了
and tell him this is just too much
快来抱堡王用餐
好  海绵宝宝
OK, SpongeBob
你能做到的
you can do this
加油
Come on
蟹老板  我能跟你谈谈吗
Mr. Krabs, could I talk to you?
进来吧  我的小子
Come on in, me boy
请坐
Have a seat
谢谢  蟹老板
Thanks, Mr. Krabs
你喜不喜欢我新办公室
Don't you just love me new office?
珍珍特地给我设计的
Pearlie designed it for me
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs, uh
我觉得我们有个问题
I think we've got a problem
你坐的这个40块钱的椅子舒不舒服
Isn't that the neatest $40 chair you ever sat in?
舒服  蟹老板
Sure, Mr. Krabs
可我有个坏消息
but I've got some bad news
我的抱抱经理兔怎么样
How about my cuddly executive bunny?
只需五次支付九块九五即可减压
Reduces stress for only five easy payment of $9.95
蟹老板  珍珍在毁掉蟹堡王
Mr. Krabs, Pearl is ruining the Krusty Krab
什么
What?
珍珍可是在拯救蟹堡王
Why, Pearl is saving the Krustry Krab
我是说  抱堡王
I mean, the Kuddly Krab
没了这些20块钱的漂亮海独角兽挂饰
What would we do without these beautiful $20
我们还怎么办
sea unicorn wall hangers?
没了这些35块的心型灯我们还怎么活
How could we have ever survived
without these $35 heart lights?
桌子不放海蕨  日子还能怎么过下去
How could we go on
without a sea fern on every last table?
特别潮
It's hip
特别炫
It's coral
特别
It's--
特别费钱
it's losing money
你说得对  海绵宝宝
You're right, SpongeBob
可我不能就这么开除我的宝贝女儿
but I can't fire me pride and joy
她脆弱的心灵会碎掉的
It would break her fragile little heart
要怎么办
What am I going to do?
好啦  蟹老板
There, there, Mr. Krabs
肯定还有别的办法
I'm sure there's another way
有了  小子
That's it, boy
什么办法
What's it?
你来开除她
You could fire her
她就算恨你也没关系
It's OK if she hates you
我不是这么说的  老板
That's not what I said, sir
那就好  安排妥当了
Great then, it's all settled
你开除珍珍
You fire Pearlie
我躲办公室里
I'll hide in the office
你也太粗鲁了  海绵宝宝
Totally rude, SpongeBob
珍珍  你能来厨房一小会儿吗
Pearl, could I see you in the kitchen for a second?
好啊  海绵宝宝
Sure, SpongeBob
要怎么向她交代
How am I going to break it to her?
我以前从来没开除过谁
I've never fired anyone before
好  我就直接开口了
Well, I just got to say it
珍珍  你被开除了
Pearl, you're fired
好  要来了
OK, here it goes
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
我再也受不了了
I can't take it anymore
我做的事全都没效果
Nothing I do is working
当然有效了  珍珍
Sure, it is, Pearl
看那些新潮小伙子吃着沙拉
Look at all the hip, young people eating salads
不对
No
不懂吗
Don't you get it?
打上班第一天起我就想让自己被开除
I've been trying to get fired since day one
我一直在假装喜欢蟹堡王
I was only pretending to like this place
好取悦老爸
to please Daddy
这工作严重打乱了我的社交生活
This job is cutting majorly into my social life
海绵宝宝  我该怎么办
Oh, SpongeBob, what should I do?
有了
I've got it
我可以假装开除你
I could pretend to fire you
等会我就去挨蟹老板的骂
I'll take the heat from old man Krabs later
天啊  你真会为我那样吗
Gosh, you'd really do that for me?
你可真好  海绵宝宝
You're a great pal, SpongeBob
我要怎么谢谢你呢
How can I ever thank you?
别把我掰成两半了
Stop trying to break me in half
成交
Deal
办公室
天啊
Oh, boy
好  珍珍
OK, Pearl
一定要装得像一点
We've got to make this convincing
珍珍  我有话要跟你说
Pearl, I need to have a word with you
不好了
Oh, no
要来了
Here it goes
我不知道我能不能忍心听下去
I don't know if I can bear to listen
不是因为你工作做得不到位
It's not that you haven't done a good job around here
只是
It's just that--
别对她那么强硬
Don't be too hard on her now
为什么非得要这样
Why does it have to be this way?
要为大局着想
It's for the best
想要为大家都好  就得
Well, we feel it might be in everybody's best interest if--
不能让他这么做
I can't let him do this
你继续吧  海绵宝宝
Get on with it, SpongeBob
珍珍  你被开除了
Pearl, you're fired
谢谢  海绵宝宝
Thanks, SpongeBob
大家来吧
Come on, gang
商场等着我们呢
The mall waits
蟹老板  我成功了
Hey, Mr. Krabs, I did it
珍珍
Pearlie
那是二十块吗
Is that a 20?
海绵宝宝
Oh, SpongeBob
怎么能对我的骨肉做出这样的事
how could we have done such a thing
to me own flesh and blood?
好啦好啦  蟹老板
There, there, Mr. Krabs
珍珍心甘情愿接受了
Pearl took it just fine
其实她好像还挺开心的
In fact, she seemed kind of happy
真的吗
Really?
她去追求更伟大的事业了
She's off to bigger and better things
这才是我的女儿  坚强无比
That's me girl, tough as nails
跟她老爸一个样
just like her old man
可买了这么多东西  要怎么回本
But how am I going to get my money back
for all this stuff?
好耶
Yeah
太好了
All right
是不是很棒啊  小蜗
Isn't this great, Gary?
而且还只花了我一年的工资
And it only cost me one year's salary